<data>
	<item id="1">
		<img>czech_republic.png</img>
		<name>Czech Republic</name>
		<area>78,866 sq km</area>
		<capital>Prague</capital>
		<language>Czech,  Slovak</language>
		<lat>48.903004</lat>
		<lng>16.686401</lng>
		<zoom>7</zoom>
		<dsc><![CDATA[Reunited after the war, the Czechs and Slovaks set federal and national elections for the spring of 1946. The democratic elements, led by President Eduard Benes, hoped the Soviet Union would allow Czechoslovakia the freedom to choose its own form of government and aspired to a Czechoslovakia that would act as a bridge between East and West. The Czechoslovak Communist Party, which won 38% of the vote, held most of the key positions in the government and gradually managed to neutralize or silence the anti-communist forces. Although the communist-led government initially intended to participate in the Marshall Plan, it was forced by Moscow to back out. Under the cover of superficial legality, the Communist Party seized power in February 1948.<p> After extensive purges modeled on the Stalinist pattern in other east European states, the Communist Party tried 14 of its former leaders in November 1952 and sentenced 11 to death. For more than a decade thereafter, the Czechoslovak communist political structure was characterized by the orthodoxy of the leadership of party chief Antonin Novotny. ]]></dsc>
		<cities><![CDATA[<rows><row><cell>Prague</cell><cell>1285995</cell><cell>75</cell><cell>68</cell></row><row><cell>Brno</cell><cell>405337</cell><cell>58</cell><cell>42</cell></row><row><cell>Ostrava</cell><cell>314666</cell><cell>61</cell><cell>59</cell></row><row><cell>Pilsen</cell><cell>173932</cell><cell>40</cell><cell>36</cell></row><row><cell>Liberec</cell><cell>105240</cell><cell>38</cell><cell>73</cell></row></rows>]]></cities>
		<chart><![CDATA[<data><item id="3"><year>2002</year><sales>9</sales></item><item id="4"><year>2003</year><sales>6</sales></item><item id="5"><year>2004</year><sales>5</sales></item><item id="6"><year>2005</year><sales>9</sales></item><item id="7"><year>2006</year><sales>5</sales></item><item id="8"><year>2007</year><sales>3</sales></item><item id="9"><year>2008</year><sales>3</sales></item><item id="10"><year>2009</year><sales>6</sales></item><item id="11"><year>2010</year><sales>4</sales></item><item id="12"><year>2011</year><sales>5</sales></item></data>]]></chart>
	</item>
	<item id="2">
		<img>belarus.png</img>
		<name>Belarus</name>
		<area>207,560 sq km</area>
		<capital>Minsk</capital>
		<language>Russian,  Byelorussian</language>
		<lat>53.867429</lat>
		<lng>27.815552</lng>
		<zoom>7</zoom>
		<dsc><![CDATA[Belarus has been inhabited since prehistoric times, and the first recorded settlements date back to the 6th century AD. The princes of Kiev ruled Belarus until the invasion of the Mongols in 1240, when most of its towns were destroyed.<p>The region came under the control of powerful Lithuanians and, in 1386, under the Lithuanian-Polish Jagiellonian Dynasty. For centuries, the Poles and the Muscovites struggled bitterly over Belarus. In 1772, Catherine the Great gained control over part of the country, and, by 1795, Russia ruled all of Belarus.<p>During the 19th and 20th centuries, the country again became a European battleground. Napoleon passed through Belarus--and fought there--in 1812, and the Germans fought the Soviets on Belarusian territory in World War I.  Although a Soviet Socialist Republic was proclaimed in January 1919, fighting with Poland continued until 1921.</p><p>Belarus suffered heavy losses in World War II, when some 2.2 million inhabitants perished. The postwar period saw a significant rebirth - especially in the economic sphere. On August 25, 1991, Belarus declared its independence from the Soviet Union. ]]></dsc>
		<cities><![CDATA[<rows><row><cell>Minsk</cell><cell>1830700</cell><cell>93</cell><cell>75</cell></row><row><cell>Mogilev</cell><cell>367788</cell><cell>68</cell><cell>64</cell></row><row><cell>Vitebsk</cell><cell>342381</cell><cell>83</cell><cell>42</cell></row><row><cell>Gomel</cell><cell>481197</cell><cell>26</cell><cell>53</cell></row><row><cell>Hrodna</cell><cell>349700</cell><cell>69</cell><cell>81</cell></row><row><cell>Brest</cell><cell>312950</cell><cell>37</cell><cell>62</cell></row></rows>]]></cities>
		<chart><![CDATA[<data><item id="3"><year>2002</year><sales>9</sales></item><item id="4"><year>2003</year><sales>2</sales></item><item id="5"><year>2004</year><sales>9</sales></item><item id="6"><year>2005</year><sales>9</sales></item><item id="7"><year>2006</year><sales>3</sales></item><item id="8"><year>2007</year><sales>3</sales></item><item id="9"><year>2008</year><sales>10</sales></item><item id="10"><year>2009</year><sales>4</sales></item><item id="11"><year>2010</year><sales>5</sales></item><item id="12"><year>2011</year><sales>6</sales></item></data>]]></chart>
	</item>
	<item id="3">
		<img>france.png</img>
		<name>France</name>
		<area>674,843 sq km</area>
		<capital>Paris</capital>
		<language>Catalan,  Flemish,  French,  Provencal</language>
		<lat>47.595</lat>
		<lng>003.028</lng>
		<zoom>6</zoom>
		<dsc><![CDATA[Although the revolutionaries advocated republican and egalitarian principles of government, France reverted to forms of absolute rule or constitutional monarchy four times--the Empire of Napoleon, the Restoration of Louis XVIII, the reign of Louis-Philippe, and the Second Empire of Napoleon III. After the Franco-Prussian War (1870), the Third Republic was established and lasted until the military defeat of 1940.</p><p>World War I (1914-18) brought great losses of troops and materiel. In the 1920s, France established an elaborate  system of border defenses (the Maginot Line) and alliances to offset resurgent German strength.</p><p>France was defeated early in World War II, however, and occupied in June 1940. The German victory left the French groping for a new policy and new leadership suited to the circumstances. On July 10, 1940, the Vichy government was established. Its senior leaders acquiesced in the plunder of French resources, as well as the sending of French forced labor to Germany; in doing so, they claimed they hoped to preserve at least some small amount of French sovereignty.]]></dsc>
		<cities><![CDATA[<rows><row><cell>Paris</cell><cell>11769433</cell><cell>95</cell><cell>86</cell></row><row><cell>Lyon</cell><cell>1748271</cell><cell>79</cell><cell>72</cell></row><row><cell>Marseille</cell><cell>1605000</cell><cell>60</cell><cell>44</cell></row><row><cell>Lille</cell><cell>1164716</cell><cell>57</cell><cell>39</cell></row><row><cell>Nice</cell><cell>1197751</cell><cell>46</cell><cell>52</cell></row><row><cell>Toulouse</cell><cell>1102882</cell><cell>53</cell><cell>48</cell></row></rows>]]></cities>
		<chart><![CDATA[<data><item id="3"><year>2002</year><sales>5</sales></item><item id="4"><year>2003</year><sales>9</sales></item><item id="5"><year>2004</year><sales>3</sales></item><item id="6"><year>2005</year><sales>5</sales></item><item id="7"><year>2006</year><sales>5</sales></item><item id="8"><year>2007</year><sales>3</sales></item><item id="9"><year>2008</year><sales>7</sales></item><item id="10"><year>2009</year><sales>5</sales></item><item id="11"><year>2010</year><sales>6</sales></item><item id="12"><year>2011</year><sales>7</sales></item></data>]]></chart>
	</item>
	<item id="4">
		<img>russia.png</img>
		<name>Russia</name>
		<area>17,098,246 sq km</area>
		<capital>Moscow</capital>
		<language>Russian</language>
		<lat>64.646</lat>
		<lng>94.541</lng>
		<zoom>3</zoom>
		<dsc><![CDATA[The U.S.S.R. lasted 69 years. In the 1930s, tens of millions of its citizens were collectivized under state agricultural and industrial enterprises. Millions died in political purges, the vast penal and labor system, or in state-created famines. During World War II, as many as 20 million Soviet citizens died. In 1949, the U.S.S.R. developed its own nuclear arsenal.</p><p>First among its political figures was Lenin, leader of the Bolshevik Party and head of the first Soviet Government, who died in 1924. In the late 1920s, Josif Stalin emerged as General Secretary of the Communist Party of the Soviet Union (CPSU) amidst intraparty rivalries; he maintained complete control over Soviet domestic and international policy until his death in 1953. His successor, Nikita Khrushchev, served as Communist Party leader until he was ousted in 1964. Aleksey Kosygin became Chairman of the Council of Ministers, and Leonid Brezhnev was made First Secretary of the CPSU Central Committee in 1964, but in 1971, Brezhnev rose to become "first among equals" in a collective leadership. Brezhnev died in 1982 and was succeeded by Yuriy Andropov (1982-84), Konstantin Chernenko (1984-85), and Mikhail Gorbachev, who resigned as Soviet President on December 25, 1991. On December 26, 1991, the U.S.S.R. was formally dissolved. ]]></dsc>
		<cities><![CDATA[<rows><row><cell>Moscow</cell><cell>10508971</cell><cell>74</cell><cell>94</cell></row><row><cell>SaintPetersburg</cell><cell>4600310</cell><cell>86</cell><cell>92</cell></row><row><cell>Novosibirsk</cell><cell>1397191</cell><cell>56</cell><cell>34</cell></row><row><cell>Yekaterinburg</cell><cell>1332264</cell><cell>67</cell><cell>49</cell></row><row><cell>NizhnyNovgorod</cell><cell>1272527</cell><cell>58</cell><cell>63</cell></row><row><cell>Samara</cell><cell>1134716</cell><cell>34</cell><cell>48</cell></row><row><cell>Kazan</cell><cell>1130170</cell><cell>62</cell><cell>39</cell></row></rows>]]></cities>
		<chart><![CDATA[<data><item id="3"><year>2002</year><sales>10</sales></item><item id="4"><year>2003</year><sales>9</sales></item><item id="5"><year>2004</year><sales>10</sales></item><item id="6"><year>2005</year><sales>10</sales></item><item id="7"><year>2006</year><sales>4</sales></item><item id="8"><year>2007</year><sales>10</sales></item><item id="9"><year>2008</year><sales>8</sales></item><item id="10"><year>2009</year><sales>10</sales></item><item id="11"><year>2010</year><sales>11</sales></item><item id="12"><year>2011</year><sales>12</sales></item></data>]]></chart>
	</item>
	<item id="5">
		<img>brazil.png</img>
		<name>Brazil</name>
		<area>8,515,767 sq km</area>
		<capital>Brasilia</capital>
		<language>English, French, Portuguese, Spanish</language>
		<lat>-15.758</lat>
		<lng>-47.954</lng>
		<zoom>5</zoom>
		<dsc><![CDATA[With an estimated 160 million inhabitants, Brazil has the largest population in Latin America and ranks sixth in the world. The majority live in the south-central area, which includes the industrial cities of Sao Paulo, Rio de Janeiro, and Belo Horizonte. Urban growth has been rapid: by 1991, 75% of the total population were living in urban areas. Rapid growth has aided economic development but has also created serious social, environmental, and political problems for major cities.</p><p>Four major groups make up the Brazilian population: the Portuguese, who colonized Brazil in the 16th century; Africans brought to Brazil as slaves; various other European, Middle Eastern, and Asian immigrant groups who have settled in Brazil since the mid-19th century; and indigenous people of Tupi and Guarani language stock. Intermarriage between the Portuguese and indigenous people or slaves was common. Although the major European ethnic stock of Brazil was once Portuguese, subsequent waves of immigration have contributed to a diverse ethnic and cultural heritage. ]]></dsc>
		<cities><![CDATA[<rows><row><cell>SaoPaulo</cell><cell>11037593</cell><cell>69</cell><cell>74</cell></row><row><cell>RiodeJaneiro</cell><cell>6187710</cell><cell>92</cell><cell>48</cell></row><row><cell>Salvador</cell><cell>2998056</cell><cell>43</cell><cell>57</cell></row><row><cell>Brasilia</cell><cell>2606885</cell><cell>80</cell><cell>64</cell></row><row><cell>Fortaleza</cell><cell>2505552</cell><cell>47</cell><cell>62</cell></row></rows>]]></cities>
		<chart><![CDATA[<data><item id="3"><year>2002</year><sales>6</sales></item><item id="4"><year>2003</year><sales>6</sales></item><item id="5"><year>2004</year><sales>10</sales></item><item id="6"><year>2005</year><sales>6</sales></item><item id="7"><year>2006</year><sales>2</sales></item><item id="8"><year>2007</year><sales>7</sales></item><item id="9"><year>2008</year><sales>9</sales></item><item id="10"><year>2009</year><sales>8</sales></item><item id="11"><year>2010</year><sales>9</sales></item><item id="12"><year>2011</year><sales>10</sales></item></data>]]></chart>
	</item>
	<item id="6">
		<img>united_states.png</img>
		<name>United States</name>
		<area>9,826,675 sq km</area>
		<capital>Washington</capital>
		<language>English, Spanish</language>
		<lat>40.757</lat>
		<lng>-100.422</lng>
		<zoom>5</zoom>
		<dsc><![CDATA[Tensions between slave and free states mounted with arguments over the relationship between the state and federal governments, as well as violent conflicts over the spread of slavery into new states. With the Confederate attack upon Fort Sumter, the American Civil War began and four more slave states joined the Confederacy. Lincoln's Emancipation Proclamation in 1863 declared slaves in the Confederacy to be free. Following the Union victory in 1865, three amendments to the U.S. Constitution ensured freedom for the nearly four million African Americans who had been slaves, made them citizens, and gave them voting rights. The war and its resolution led to a substantial increase in federal power.</p><p>Immigrants at Ellis Island, New York Harbor, 1902</p><p>After the war, the assassination of Lincoln radicalized Republican Reconstruction policies aimed at reintegrating and rebuilding the Southern states while ensuring the rights of the newly freed slaves. The resolution of the disputed 1876 presidential election by the Compromise of 1877 ended Reconstruction; Jim Crow laws soon disenfranchised many African Americans. In the North, urbanization and an unprecedented influx of immigrants from Southern and Eastern Europe hastened the country's industrialization. The wave of immigration, lasting until 1929, provided labor and transformed American culture. National infrastructure development spurred economic growth. The 1867 Alaska purchase from Russia completed the country's mainland expansion. The Wounded Knee massacre in 1890 was the last major armed conflict of the Indian Wars. In 1893, the indigenous monarchy of the Pacific Kingdom of Hawaii was overthrown in a coup led by American residents; the United States annexed the archipelago in 1898. Victory in the Spanish-American War the same year demonstrated that the United States was a world power and led to the annexation of Puerto Rico, Guam, and the Philippines. The Philippines gained independence a half-century later; Puerto Rico and Guam remain U.S. territories.]]></dsc>
		<cities><![CDATA[<rows><row><cell>NewYork</cell><cell>19006798</cell><cell>90</cell><cell>83</cell></row><row><cell>LosAngeles</cell><cell>12872808</cell><cell>91</cell><cell>87</cell></row><row><cell>Chicago</cell><cell>9569624</cell><cell>92</cell><cell>86</cell></row><row><cell>Dallas</cell><cell>6300006</cell><cell>62</cell><cell>78</cell></row><row><cell>Philadelphia</cell><cell>5838471</cell><cell>59</cell><cell>63</cell></row><row><cell>Houston</cell><cell>5728143</cell><cell>42</cell><cell>39</cell></row></rows>]]></cities>
		<chart><![CDATA[<data><item id="3"><year>2002</year><sales>3</sales></item><item id="4"><year>2003</year><sales>7</sales></item><item id="5"><year>2004</year><sales>6</sales></item><item id="6"><year>2005</year><sales>7</sales></item><item id="7"><year>2006</year><sales>6</sales></item><item id="8"><year>2007</year><sales>8</sales></item><item id="9"><year>2008</year><sales>6</sales></item><item id="10"><year>2009</year><sales>10</sales></item><item id="11"><year>2010</year><sales>11</sales></item><item id="12"><year>2011</year><sales>12</sales></item></data>]]></chart>
	</item>
	<item id="7">
		<img>canada.png</img>
		<name>Canada</name>
		<area>9,984,670 sq km</area>
		<capital>Ottawa</capital>
		<language>English(official), French(official)</language>
		<lat>62.075</lat>
		<lng>-112.426</lng>
		<zoom>4</zoom>
		<dsc><![CDATA[Canada is a constitutional monarchy with a federal system, a parliamentary government, and strong democratic traditions. Many of the country's legal practices are based on unwritten custom, but the federal structure resembles the U.S. system. The 1982 Charter of Rights guarantees basic rights in many areas.</p><p>Queen Elizabeth II, as Queen of Canada, serves as a symbol of the nation's unity. She appoints a governor general on the advice of the prime minister of Canada, usually for a 5-year term. The prime minister is the leader of the political party in power and is the head of the cabinet. The cabinet remains in office as long as it retains majority support in the House of Commons on major issues. ]]></dsc>
		<cities><![CDATA[<rows><row><cell>Toronto</cell><cell>5113149</cell><cell>91</cell><cell>64</cell></row><row><cell>Montreal</cell><cell>3635571</cell><cell>73</cell><cell>47</cell></row><row><cell>Vancouver</cell><cell>2116581</cell><cell>89</cell><cell>90</cell></row><row><cell>Calgary</cell><cell>1079310</cell><cell>74</cell><cell>58</cell></row><row><cell>Edmonton</cell><cell>1034945</cell><cell>45</cell><cell>61</cell></row></rows>]]></cities>
		<chart><![CDATA[<data><item id="3"><year>2002</year><sales>8</sales></item><item id="4"><year>2003</year><sales>8</sales></item><item id="5"><year>2004</year><sales>9</sales></item><item id="6"><year>2005</year><sales>10</sales></item><item id="7"><year>2006</year><sales>6</sales></item><item id="8"><year>2007</year><sales>4</sales></item><item id="9"><year>2008</year><sales>7</sales></item><item id="10"><year>2009</year><sales>10</sales></item><item id="11"><year>2010</year><sales>12</sales></item><item id="12"><year>2011</year><sales>13</sales></item></data>]]></chart>
	</item>
	<item id="8">
		<img>united_arab_emirates.png</img>
		<name>United Arab Emirates</name>
		<area>83,600 sq km </area>
		<capital>Abu Dhab</capital>
		<language>Arabic, English, Hindi, Persian, Urdu</language>
		<lat>24.152</lat>
		<lng>54.488</lng>
		<zoom>7</zoom>
		<dsc><![CDATA[Primarily in reaction to the ambitions of other European countries, the United Kingdom and the Trucial Shaikhdoms established closer bonds in an 1892 treaty, similar to treaties entered into by the UK with other Gulf principalities.  The shaikhs agreed not to dispose of any territory except to the United Kingdom and not to enter into relationships with any foreign government other than the United Kingdom without its consent.  In return, the British promised to protect the Trucial Coast from all aggression by sea and to help out in case of land attack.</p><p>In 1955, the United Kingdom sided with Abu Dhabi in the latter's dispute with Saudi Arabia over the Buraimi Oasis and other territory to the south.  A 1974 agreement between Abu Dhabi and Saudi Arabia would have settled the Abu Dhabi-Saudi border dispute; however, the agreement has yet to be ratified by the UAE Government and apparently is not recognized by the Saudi Government.  The border with Oman also remains unsettled.</p><p>In 1968, the UK announced its decision, reaffirmed in March 1971, to end the treaty relationships with the seven Trucial Shaikhdoms which had been, together with Bahrain and Qatar, under British protection.  The nine attempted to form a union of Arab emirates, but by mid-1971 they were unable to agree on terms of union, even though the termination date of the British treaty relationship was the end of 1971.  Bahrain became independent in August and Qatar in September 1971.  When the British-Trucial Shaikhdoms treaty expired on December 1, 1971, they became fully independent.  On December 2, 1971, six of them entered into a union called the United Arab Emirates.  The seventh, Ras al-Khaimah, joined in early 1972.]]></dsc>
		<cities><![CDATA[<rows><row><cell>Dubai</cell><cell>872700</cell><cell>90</cell><cell>87</cell></row><row><cell>AbuDhabi</cell><cell>519900</cell><cell>65</cell><cell>58</cell></row><row><cell>Sharjah</cell><cell>417400</cell><cell>48</cell><cell>32</cell></row><row><cell>AlAin</cell><cell>294700</cell><cell>29</cell><cell>44</cell></row><row><cell>Ajman</cell><cell>149200</cell><cell>62</cell><cell>57</cell></row></rows>]]></cities>
		<chart><![CDATA[<data><item id="3"><year>2002</year><sales>8</sales></item><item id="4"><year>2003</year><sales>3</sales></item><item id="5"><year>2004</year><sales>5</sales></item><item id="6"><year>2005</year><sales>5</sales></item><item id="7"><year>2006</year><sales>4</sales></item><item id="8"><year>2007</year><sales>8</sales></item><item id="9"><year>2008</year><sales>8</sales></item><item id="10"><year>2009</year><sales>4</sales></item><item id="11"><year>2010</year><sales>4</sales></item><item id="12"><year>2011</year><sales>5</sales></item></data>]]></chart>
	</item>
	<item id="9">
		<img>zimbabwe.png</img>
		<name>Zimbabwe</name>
		<area>390,580 sq km</area>
		<capital>Harare</capital>
		<language>English, Ndebele, Shona</language>
		<lat>-18.931</lat>
		<lng>30.054</lng>
		<zoom>7</zoom>
		<dsc><![CDATA[More than half of the whites, primarily of English origin, arrived in Zimbabwe after World War II. Afrikaners from South Africa and other European minorities, including Portuguese from Mozambique, are also present. Until the mid-1970's, there were about 1,000 white immigrants per year, but from 1976 to 1985 a steady emigration resulted in a loss of more than 150,000, leaving approximately 100,000 in 1992. English, the official language, is spoken by the white population and understood, if not always used, by more than half of the blacks.</p><p>The literacy rate is estimated at 70%. Primary and secondary schools were segregated until 1979 when racial restrictions were removed. Since independence, the educational system had been systematically enlarged by the Zimbabwean Government which is committed to providing free public education to all citizens on an equal basis. As of the late 1970s, some 50 percent of the African children (5-19 years old) were listed officially as attending rural schools. Today, most African children attend primary school. Primary through post-secondary enrollment has expanded from 1 million to about 2.9 million since independence. About 40 percent of the rural primary schools were destroyed during the Rhodesian conflict, which delayed improvement of the rural education system. Higher education, offered at the University of Zimbabwe in Harare, the new National University of Science and Technology in Bulawayo, the new Africa (Methodist) University in Mutare, several teacher-training colleges, and three technical institutes, are being expanded with assistance from several donor countries.]]></dsc>
		<cities><![CDATA[<rows><row><cell>Bulawayo</cell><cell>676000</cell><cell>45</cell><cell>62</cell></row><row><cell>Gweru</cell><cell>300000</cell><cell>37</cell><cell>49</cell></row><row><cell>Harare</cell><cell>1600000</cell><cell>31</cell><cell>42</cell></row><row><cell>Marondera</cell><cell>46000</cell><cell>51</cell><cell>47</cell></row><row><cell>Mutare</cell><cell>170106</cell><cell>60</cell><cell>38</cell></row></rows>]]></cities>
		<chart><![CDATA[<data><item id="3"><year>2002</year><sales>10</sales></item><item id="4"><year>2003</year><sales>10</sales></item><item id="5"><year>2004</year><sales>7</sales></item><item id="6"><year>2005</year><sales>2</sales></item><item id="7"><year>2006</year><sales>10</sales></item><item id="8"><year>2007</year><sales>3</sales></item><item id="9"><year>2008</year><sales>3</sales></item><item id="10"><year>2009</year><sales>10</sales></item><item id="11"><year>2010</year><sales>11</sales></item><item id="12"><year>2011</year><sales>13</sales></item></data>]]></chart>
	</item>
	<item id="10">
		<img>poland.png</img>
		<name>Poland</name>
		<area>312,685 sq km</area>
		<capital>Warsaw</capital>
		<language>Polish</language>
		<lat>52.114</lat>
		<lng>19.812</lng>
		<zoom>7</zoom>
		<dsc><![CDATA[In April 1943, the Soviet Union broke relations with the Polish government in exile after the German military announced that they had discovered mass graves of murdered Polish army officers at Katyn, in the U.S.S.R. (The Soviets claimed that the Poles had insulted them by requesting that the Red Cross investigate these reports.) In July 1944, the Soviet Red Army entered Poland and established a communist controlled "Polish Committee of National Liberation" at Lublin.</p><p>Resistance against the Nazis in Warsaw, including uprisings by Jews in the Warsaw ghetto and by the Polish underground, was brutally suppressed. As the Germans retreated in January 1945, they leveled the city.</p><p>During the war, about 6 million Poles were killed, and 2.5 million were deported to Germany for forced labor. More than 3 million Jews (all but about 100,000 of the Jewish population) were killed in death camps like those at Oswiecim (Auschwitz), Treblinka, and Majdanek.</p><p>Following the Yalta Conference in February 1945, a Polish Provisional Government of National Unity was formed in June 1945; the U.S. recognized it the next month. Although the Yalta agreement called for free elections, those held in January 1947 were controlled by the Communist Party. The communists then established a regime entirely under their domination. ]]></dsc>
		<cities><![CDATA[<rows><row><cell>Warsaw</cell><cell>2631902</cell><cell>67</cell><cell>49</cell></row><row><cell>Krakow</cell><cell>754854</cell><cell>58</cell><cell>81</cell></row><row><cell>Lodz</cell><cell>744541</cell><cell>49</cell><cell>32</cell></row><row><cell>Gdansk</cell><cell>455830</cell><cell>61</cell><cell>39</cell></row><row><cell>Poznan</cell><cell>556022</cell><cell>49</cell><cell>57</cell></row><row><cell>Wroclaw</cell><cell>632240</cell><cell>34</cell><cell>46</cell></row></rows>]]></cities>
		<chart><![CDATA[<data><item id="3"><year>2002</year><sales>5</sales></item><item id="4"><year>2003</year><sales>10</sales></item><item id="5"><year>2004</year><sales>2</sales></item><item id="6"><year>2005</year><sales>4</sales></item><item id="7"><year>2006</year><sales>2</sales></item><item id="8"><year>2007</year><sales>9</sales></item><item id="9"><year>2008</year><sales>5</sales></item><item id="10"><year>2009</year><sales>6</sales></item><item id="11"><year>2010</year><sales>7</sales></item><item id="12"><year>2011</year><sales>8</sales></item></data>]]></chart>
	</item>
	<item id="11">
		<img>argentina.png</img>
		<name>Argentina</name>
		<area>2,780,400 sq km</area>
		<capital>Buenos Aires</capital>
		<language>English, French, Italian, Spanish</language>
		<lat>-33.702</lat>
		<lng>-64.350</lng>
		<zoom>5</zoom>
		<dsc><![CDATA[As President, Menem launched a major overhaul of Argentine domestic policy. Large-scale structural reforms dramatically reversed the role of the state in Argentine economic life. A decisive leader pressing a controversial agenda, Menem was not reluctant to use the presidency's extensive powers to issue decrees when the Congress was unable to reach consensus on his proposed reforms. Those powers were curtailed somewhat when the constitution was reformed in 1994 as a result of the so-called Olivos Pact with the opposition Radical Party. That arrangement opened the way for Menem to seek and win reelection with 50% of the vote in the three-way 1995 presidential race.</p><p>The 1995 election saw the emergence of the moderate-left FREPASO political alliance. This alternative to the two traditional political parties in Argentina is particularly strong in Buenos Aires but as yet lacks the national infrastructure of the Peronists and Radicals. In an important development in Argentina's political life, all three major parties in the 1999 race espoused free market economic policies. In October 1999, the UCR-FREPASO Alliance's presidential candidate, Fernando de la Rua, defeated Peronist candidate Eduardo Duhalde. Taking office in December 1999, De la Rua has not only continued the previous administration's free market economic policies but has followed an IMF-sponsored program of government spending cuts, revenue increases, and provincial revenue-sharing reforms to get the federal deficit under control. De la Rua also has pursued labor law reform and business-promotion measures aimed at stimulating the economy and increasing employment. Despite these measures, Argentine economic growth remained nearly flat in 2000. ]]></dsc>
		<cities><![CDATA[<rows><row><cell>BuenosAires</cell><cell>3050728</cell><cell>36</cell><cell>82</cell></row><row><cell>Cordoba</cell><cell>1346092</cell><cell>57</cell><cell>45</cell></row><row><cell>Rosario</cell><cell>1249594</cell><cell>60</cell><cell>89</cell></row><row><cell>Mendoza</cell><cell>885434</cell><cell>30</cell><cell>78</cell></row><row><cell>Tucuman</cell><cell>789504</cell><cell>46</cell><cell>41</cell></row><row><cell>LaPlata</cell><cell>732503</cell><cell>65</cell><cell>83</cell></row></rows>]]></cities>
		<chart><![CDATA[<data><item id="3"><year>2002</year><sales>8</sales></item><item id="4"><year>2003</year><sales>4</sales></item><item id="5"><year>2004</year><sales>7</sales></item><item id="6"><year>2005</year><sales>9</sales></item><item id="7"><year>2006</year><sales>7</sales></item><item id="8"><year>2007</year><sales>2</sales></item><item id="9"><year>2008</year><sales>2</sales></item><item id="10"><year>2009</year><sales>9</sales></item><item id="11"><year>2010</year><sales>10</sales></item><item id="12"><year>2011</year><sales>11</sales></item></data>]]></chart>
	</item>
	<item id="12">
		<img>switzerland.png</img>
		<name>Switzerland</name>
		<area>41,285 sq km</area>
		<capital>Bern</capital>
		<language>French, German, Italian, Romansch</language>
		<lat>46.909</lat>
		<lng>8.477</lng>
		<zoom>8</zoom>
		<dsc><![CDATA[In 1291, representatives of the three forest cantons of Uri, Schwyz, and Unterwalden signed the Eternal Alliance. This united them in the struggle against "foreign" rule by the Hapsburgs, who then held the German imperial throne. At the battle of Morganten in 1315, the Swiss defeated the Hapsburg army and secured quasi-independence within the German Empire as the Swiss Confederation.</p><p>Under the Treaty of Westphalia in 1648, European countries recognized Switzerland's independence from the Holy Roman Empire and its neutrality.</p><p>In 1798, armies of the French Revolution conquered Switzerland. The Treaty of Vienna and the Second Peace of Paris in 1815 re-established Swiss independence, and the powers participating in the Congress of Vienna agreed to recognize Swiss permanent neutrality.</p><p>Switzerland adopted a federal constitution in 1848, modeled in part on the U.S. Constitution. The Swiss amended their constitution extensively in 1874, establishing federal responsibility for defense, trade, and legal matters. Since then, continued political, economic, and social improvement has characterized Swiss history. The Swiss did not participate in either world war. ]]></dsc>
		<cities><![CDATA[<rows><row><cell>Bern</cell><cell>349000</cell><cell>82</cell><cell>70</cell></row><row><cell>Lausanne</cell><cell>122284</cell><cell>49</cell><cell>62</cell></row><row><cell>Zurich</cell><cell>365098</cell><cell>46</cell><cell>68</cell></row><row><cell>Fribourg</cell><cell>34084</cell><cell>59</cell><cell>38</cell></row><row><cell>Geneva</cell><cell>187697</cell><cell>84</cell><cell>87</cell></row><row><cell>Lucerne</cell><cell>76156</cell><cell>49</cell><cell>68</cell></row></rows>]]></cities>
		<chart><![CDATA[<data><item id="3"><year>2002</year><sales>5</sales></item><item id="4"><year>2003</year><sales>7</sales></item><item id="5"><year>2004</year><sales>6</sales></item><item id="6"><year>2005</year><sales>2</sales></item><item id="7"><year>2006</year><sales>6</sales></item><item id="8"><year>2007</year><sales>5</sales></item><item id="9"><year>2008</year><sales>9</sales></item><item id="10"><year>2009</year><sales>8</sales></item><item id="11"><year>2010</year><sales>9</sales></item><item id="12"><year>2011</year><sales>10</sales></item></data>]]></chart>
	</item>
	<item id="13">
		<img>turkey.png</img>
		<name>Turkey</name>
		<area>783,562 sq km</area>
		<capital>Ankara</capital>
		<language>Arabic, Turkish, Kurdish</language>
		<lat>39.203</lat>
		<lng>34.537</lng>
		<zoom>6</zoom>
		<dsc><![CDATA[The legendary Mustafa Kemal, a Turkish World War I hero later known as "Ataturk" or "father of the Turks," founded the Republic of Turkey in 1923 after the collapse of the 600-year-old Ottoman Empire. The empire, which at its peak controlled vast stretches of northern Africa, southeastern Europe, and western Asia, had failed to keep pace with European social and technological developments. The rise of nationalism impelled several ethnic groups to seek independence, leading to the empire's fragmentation. This process culminated in the disastrous Ottoman participation in World War I as a German ally. Defeated, shorn of much of its former territory, and partly occupied by forces of the victorious European states, the Ottoman structure was repudiated by Turkish nationalists who rallied under Ataturk's leadership. The nationalists expelled invading Greek forces from Anatolia after a bitter war. The temporal and religious ruling institutions of the old empire (the sultanate and caliphate) were abolished.</p><p>The new republic concentrated on Westernizing the empire's Turkish core -- Anatolia and a small part of Thrace. Social, political, linguistic, and economic reforms and attitudes introduced by Ataturk before his death in 1938 continue to form the ideological base of modern Turkey. Referred to as "Kemalism," it comprises secularism, nationalism, and modernization and turns toward the West for inspiration and support. The continued validity and applicability of Kemalism are the subject of frequent discussion and debate in Turkey's political life.</p><p>Turkey entered World War II on the Allied side shortly before the war ended and became a charter member of the United Nations. Difficulties faced by Greece after World War II in quelling a communist rebellion and demands by the Soviet Union for military bases in the Turkish Straits caused the United States to declare the Truman Doctrine in 1947. The doctrine enunciated American intentions to guarantee the security of Turkey and Greece and resulted in largescale U.S. military and economic aid. After participating with United Nations forces in the Korean conflict, Turkey in 1952 joined the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO). ]]></dsc>
		<cities><![CDATA[<rows><row><cell>Ankara</cell><cell>3763591</cell><cell>63</cell><cell>53</cell></row><row><cell>Istanbul</cell><cell>12782960</cell><cell>46</cell><cell>57</cell></row><row><cell>Izmir</cell><cell>2699721</cell><cell>39</cell><cell>40</cell></row><row><cell>Bursa</cell><cell>1642020</cell><cell>31</cell><cell>29</cell></row><row><cell>Adana</cell><cell>1529302</cell><cell>47</cell><cell>40</cell></row></rows>]]></cities>
		<chart><![CDATA[<data><item id="3"><year>2002</year><sales>10</sales></item><item id="4"><year>2003</year><sales>4</sales></item><item id="5"><year>2004</year><sales>5</sales></item><item id="6"><year>2005</year><sales>6</sales></item><item id="7"><year>2006</year><sales>8</sales></item><item id="8"><year>2007</year><sales>8</sales></item><item id="9"><year>2008</year><sales>8</sales></item><item id="10"><year>2009</year><sales>7</sales></item><item id="11"><year>2010</year><sales>8</sales></item><item id="12"><year>2011</year><sales>9</sales></item></data>]]></chart>
	</item>
	<item id="14">
		<img>united_kingdom.png</img>
		<name>United Kingdom</name>
		<area>243,610 sq km</area>
		<capital>London</capital>
		<language>English, Welsh, Scottish</language>
		<lat>54.114</lat>
		<lng>-2.222</lng>
		<zoom>6</zoom>
		<dsc><![CDATA[By the time of Queen Victoria's death in 1901, other nations, including the United States and Germany, had developed their own industries; the United Kingdom's comparative economic advantage had lessened, and the ambitions of its rivals had grown. The losses and destruction of World War I, the depression of the 1930s, and decades of relatively slow growth eroded the United Kingdom's preeminent international position of the previous century.</p><p>Britain's control over its empire loosened during the interwar period. Ireland, with the exception of six northern counties, gained independence from the United Kingdom in 1921. Nationalism became stronger in other parts of the Empire, particularly in India and Egypt.</p><p>In 1926, the U.K., completing a process begun a century earlier, granted Australia, Canada, and New Zealand complete autonomy within the Empire. They became charter members of the British Commonwealth of Nations (now known as the Commonwealth), an informal but closely knit association that succeeded the Empire. Beginning with the independence of India and Pakistan in 1947, the remainder of the British Empire was almost completely dismantled. Today, most of Britain's former colonies belong to the Commonwealth, almost all of them as independent members. There are, however, 13 former British colonies--including Bermuda, Gibraltar, the Falkland Islands, and others--which have elected to continue their political links with London and are known as United Kingdom Overseas Territories. ]]></dsc>
		<cities><![CDATA[<rows><row><cell>London</cell><cell>7172091</cell><cell>87</cell><cell>93</cell></row><row><cell>Birmingham</cell><cell>970892</cell><cell>56</cell><cell>67</cell></row><row><cell>Glasgow</cell><cell>629501</cell><cell>49</cell><cell>53</cell></row><row><cell>Liverpool</cell><cell>469017</cell><cell>80</cell><cell>72</cell></row><row><cell>Leeds</cell><cell>443247</cell><cell>53</cell><cell>57</cell></row><row><cell>Sheffield</cell><cell>439866</cell><cell>47</cell><cell>35</cell></row></rows>]]></cities>
		<chart><![CDATA[<data><item id="3"><year>2002</year><sales>5</sales></item><item id="4"><year>2003</year><sales>8</sales></item><item id="5"><year>2004</year><sales>4</sales></item><item id="6"><year>2005</year><sales>7</sales></item><item id="7"><year>2006</year><sales>9</sales></item><item id="8"><year>2007</year><sales>5</sales></item><item id="9"><year>2008</year><sales>3</sales></item><item id="10"><year>2009</year><sales>6</sales></item><item id="11"><year>2010</year><sales>7</sales></item><item id="12"><year>2011</year><sales>9</sales></item></data>]]></chart>
	</item>
	<item id="15">
		<img>spain.png</img>
		<name>Spain</name>
		<area>504,782 sq km</area>
		<capital>Madrid</capital>
		<language>Catalan, Spanish, Basque, Galician</language>
		<lat>40.217</lat>
		<lng>-3.497</lng>
		<zoom>6</zoom>
		<dsc><![CDATA[The Iberian Peninsula has been occupied for many millennia. Some of Europe's most impressive Paleolithic cultural sites are located there; the famous caves at Altamira contain spectacular paintings which date from about 15,000-25,000 years ago. The Basques are the first identifiable people of the peninsula and are the oldest surviving group in Europe. Iberians arrived from North Africa during a more recent period.</p><p>Beginning in the ninth century BC, Phoenicians, Greeks, Carthaginians, and Celts entered the Iberian Peninsula, followed by the Romans, who arrived in the second century BC. Spain's present language, religion, and laws stem from the Roman period. Although the Visigoths arrived in the fifth century AD, the last Roman strongholds along the southern coast did not fall until the seventh century AD. In 711, North African Moors sailed across the straits, swept into Andalusia, and, within a few years, pushed the Visigoths up the peninsula to the Cantabrian Mountains. The Reconquest--efforts to drive out the Moors--lasted until 1492. By 1512, the unification of present-day Spain was complete.</p><p>During the 16th century, Spain became the most powerful nation in Europe, due to the immense wealth derived from its presence in the Americas. But a series of long, costly wars and revolts, capped by the defeat by the English of the "Invincible Armada" in 1588, began a steady decline of Spanish power in Europe. Controversy over succession to the throne consumed the country during the 18th century, leading to an occupation by France during the Napoleonic era in the early 1800s, and led to a series of armed conflicts throughout much of the 19th century. ]]></dsc>
		<cities><![CDATA[<rows><row><cell>Madrid</cell><cell>3213271</cell><cell>90</cell><cell>74</cell></row><row><cell>Barcelona</cell><cell>1615908</cell><cell>69</cell><cell>74</cell></row><row><cell>Valencia</cell><cell>810064</cell><cell>63</cell><cell>49</cell></row><row><cell>Seville</cell><cell>699759</cell><cell>59</cell><cell>62</cell></row><row><cell>Zaragoza</cell><cell>666129</cell><cell>43</cell><cell>58</cell></row></rows>]]></cities>
		<chart><![CDATA[<data><item id="3"><year>2002</year><sales>3</sales></item><item id="4"><year>2003</year><sales>3</sales></item><item id="5"><year>2004</year><sales>3</sales></item><item id="6"><year>2005</year><sales>9</sales></item><item id="7"><year>2006</year><sales>6</sales></item><item id="8"><year>2007</year><sales>2</sales></item><item id="9"><year>2008</year><sales>8</sales></item><item id="10"><year>2009</year><sales>7</sales></item><item id="11"><year>2010</year><sales>6</sales></item><item id="12"><year>2011</year><sales>6</sales></item></data>]]></chart>
	</item>
	<item id="16">
		<img>chile.png</img>
		<name>Chile</name>
		<area>756,096 sq km</area>
		<capital>Santiago</capital>
		<language>Spanish</language>
		<lat>-28.447</lat>
		<lng>-70.451</lng>
		<zoom>5</zoom>
		<dsc><![CDATA[About 10,000 years ago, migrating Indians settled in fertile valleys and along the coast of what is now Chile. The Incas briefly extended their empire into what is now northern Chile, but the area's remoteness prevented extensive settlement. In 1541, the Spanish, under Pedro de Valdivia, encountered hundreds of thousands of Indians from various cultures in the area that modern Chile now occupies. These cultures supported themselves principally through slash-and-burn agriculture and hunting. Although the Spanish did not find the extensive gold and silver they sought, they recognized the agricultural potential of Chile's central valley, and Chile became part of the Viceroyalty of Peru.</p><p>The drive for independence from Spain was precipitated by usurpation of the Spanish throne by Napoleon's brother Joseph. A national junta in the name of Ferdinand--heir to the deposed king--was formed on September 18, 1810. Spanish attempts to reimpose arbitrary rule during what was called the Reconquista led to a prolonged struggle under Bernardo O'Higgins, Chile's most renowned patriot. Chilean independence was formally proclaimed on February 12, 1818.</p><p>The political revolt brought little social change, however, and 19th century Chilean society preserved the essence of the stratified colonial social structure, family politics, and the influence of the Roman Catholic Church. The system of presidential power eventually predominated, but wealthy landowners continued to control Chile.]]></dsc>
		<cities><![CDATA[<rows><row><cell>Arica</cell><cell>185268</cell><cell>37</cell><cell>62</cell></row><row><cell>LaSerena</cell><cell>177608</cell><cell>49</cell><cell>26</cell></row><row><cell>Santiago</cell><cell>5278044</cell><cell>73</cell><cell>60</cell></row><row><cell>Valparaiso</cell><cell>275982</cell><cell>51</cell><cell>42</cell></row><row><cell>PuertoMontt</cell><cell>175938</cell><cell>39</cell><cell>27</cell></row></rows>]]></cities>
		<chart><![CDATA[<data><item id="3"><year>2002</year><sales>7</sales></item><item id="4"><year>2003</year><sales>10</sales></item><item id="5"><year>2004</year><sales>4</sales></item><item id="6"><year>2005</year><sales>8</sales></item><item id="7"><year>2006</year><sales>8</sales></item><item id="8"><year>2007</year><sales>10</sales></item><item id="9"><year>2008</year><sales>9</sales></item><item id="10"><year>2009</year><sales>2</sales></item><item id="11"><year>2010</year><sales>4</sales></item><item id="12"><year>2011</year><sales>5</sales></item></data>]]></chart>
	</item>
	<item id="17">
		<img>china.png</img>
		<name>China</name>
		<area>9,706,961 sq km</area>
		<capital>Beijing</capital>
		<language>Chinese, Yue, Wu, Minbei</language>
		<lat>35.267</lat>
		<lng>102.729</lng>
		<zoom>4</zoom>
		<dsc><![CDATA[China is the oldest continuous major world civilization, with records dating back about 3,500 years. Successive dynasties developed a system of bureaucratic control which gave the agrarian-based Chinese an advantage over neighboring nomadic and hill cultures. Chinese civilization was further strengthened by the development of a Confucian state ideology and a common written language that bridged the gaps among the country's many local languages and dialects. Whenever China was conquered by nomadic tribes, as it was by the Mongols in the 13th century, the conquerors sooner or later adopted the ways of the "higher" Chinese civilization and staffed the bureaucracy with Chinese.</p><p>The last dynasty was established in 1644, when the nomadic Manchus overthrew the native Ming dynasty and established the Qing (Ch'ing) dynasty with Beijing as its capital. At great expense in blood and treasure, the Manchus over the next half century gained control of many border areas, including Xinjiang, Yunnan, Tibet, Mongolia, and Taiwan. The success of the early Qing period was based on the combination of Manchu martial prowess and traditional Chinese bureaucratic skills.</p><p>During the 19th century, Qing control weakened, and prosperity diminished. China suffered massive social strife, economic stagnation, explosive population growth, and Western penetration and influence. The Taiping and Nian rebellions, along with a Russian-supported Muslim separatist movement in Xinjiang, drained Chinese resources and almost toppled the dynasty. Britain's desire to continue its illegal opium trade with China collided with imperial edicts prohibiting the addictive drug, and the First Opium War erupted in 1840. China lost the war; subsequently, Britain and other Western powers, including the United States, forcibly occupied "concessions" and gained special commercial privileges. Hong Kong was ceded to Britain in 1842 under the Treaty of Nanking, and in 1898, when the Opium Wars finally ended, Britain executed a 99-year lease of the New Territories, significantly expanding the size of the Hong Kong colony.</p><p>As time went on, the Western powers, wielding superior military technology, gained more economic and political privileges. Reformist Chinese officials argued for the adoption of Western technology to strengthen the dynasty and counter Western advances, but the Qing court played down both the Western threat and the benefits of Western technology. ]]></dsc>
		<cities><![CDATA[<rows><row><cell>Shanghai</cell><cell>17000000</cell><cell>65</cell><cell>37</cell></row><row><cell>Beijing</cell><cell>13200000</cell><cell>89</cell><cell>45</cell></row><row><cell>HongKong</cell><cell>7055071</cell><cell>82</cell><cell>67</cell></row><row><cell>Shenzhen</cell><cell>8615000</cell><cell>45</cell><cell>53</cell></row><row><cell>Tianjin</cell><cell>8200000</cell><cell>30</cell><cell>42</cell></row><row><cell>Wuhan</cell><cell>6600000</cell><cell>40</cell><cell>64</cell></row></rows>]]></cities>
		<chart><![CDATA[<data><item id="3"><year>2002</year><sales>3</sales></item><item id="4"><year>2003</year><sales>6</sales></item><item id="5"><year>2004</year><sales>8</sales></item><item id="6"><year>2005</year><sales>4</sales></item><item id="7"><year>2006</year><sales>3</sales></item><item id="8"><year>2007</year><sales>10</sales></item><item id="9"><year>2008</year><sales>5</sales></item><item id="10"><year>2009</year><sales>8</sales></item><item id="11"><year>2010</year><sales>7</sales></item><item id="12"><year>2011</year><sales>9</sales></item></data>]]></chart>
	</item>
	<item id="18">
		<img>togo.png</img>
		<name>Togo</name>
		<area>56,785 sq km</area>
		<capital>Lome</capital>
		<language>Ewe, French, Mina, Kabye</language>
		<lat>8.283</lat>
		<lng>1.094</lng>
		<zoom>7</zoom>
		<dsc><![CDATA[The Ewes moved into the area which is now Togo from the Niger river valley between the 12th and 14th centuries. During the 15th and 16th centuries, Portuguese explorers and traders visited the coast. For the next 200 years, the coastal region was a major raiding center for Europeans in search of slaves, earning Togo and the surrounding region the name "The Slave Coast."</p><p>In an 1884 treaty signed at Togoville, Germany declared a protectorate over a stretch of territory along the coast and gradually extended its control inland. Because it became Germany's only self- supporting colony, Togoland was known as its model possession. In 1914, Togoland was invaded by French and British forces and fell after brief resistance. Following the war, Togoland became a League of Nations mandate divided for administrative purposes between France and the United Kingdom.</p><p>After World War II, the mandate became a UN trust territory administered by the United Kingdom and France. During the mandate and trusteeship periods, Western Togo was administered as part of the British Gold Coast. In 1957, the residents of British Togoland voted to join the Gold Coast as part of the new independent nation of Ghana.</p><p>By statute in 1955, French Togo became an autonomous republic within the French union, although it retained its UN trusteeship status. A legislative assembly elected by universal adult suffrage had considerable power over internal affairs, with an elected executive body headed by a prime minister responsible to the legislature. These changes were embodied in a constitution approved in a 1956 referendum. On September 10, 1956, Nicholas Grunitzky became prime minister of the Republic of Togo. However, due to irregularities in the plebiscite, an unsupervised general election was held in 1958 and won by Sylvanus Olympio. On April 27, 1960, in a smooth transition, Togo severed its judicial ties with France, shed its UN trusteeship status, and became fully independent under a provisional constitution with Olympio as president. ]]></dsc>
		<cities><![CDATA[<rows><row><cell>Lome</cell><cell>729258</cell><cell>62</cell><cell>55</cell></row><row><cell>Sokode</cell><cell>117811</cell><cell>40</cell><cell>37</cell></row><row><cell>Kara</cell><cell>104207</cell><cell>26</cell><cell>45</cell></row><row><cell>Palime</cell><cell>95974</cell><cell>60</cell><cell>34</cell></row><row><cell>Bassar</cell><cell>61845</cell><cell>31</cell><cell>49</cell></row></rows>]]></cities>
		<chart><![CDATA[<data><item id="3"><year>2002</year><sales>8</sales></item><item id="4"><year>2003</year><sales>4</sales></item><item id="5"><year>2004</year><sales>5</sales></item><item id="6"><year>2005</year><sales>8</sales></item><item id="7"><year>2006</year><sales>10</sales></item><item id="8"><year>2007</year><sales>3</sales></item><item id="9"><year>2008</year><sales>5</sales></item><item id="10"><year>2009</year><sales>3</sales></item><item id="11"><year>2010</year><sales>4</sales></item><item id="12"><year>2011</year><sales>5</sales></item></data>]]></chart>
	</item>
	<item id="19">
		<img>japan.png</img>
		<name>Japan</name>
		<area>377,944 sq km</area>
		<capital>Tokyo</capital>
		<language>Japanese</language>
		<lat>36.479</lat>
		<lng>138.973</lng>
		<zoom>6</zoom>
		<dsc><![CDATA[Traditional Japanese legend maintains that Japan was founded in 600 BC by the Emperor Jimmu, a direct descendant of the sun goddess and ancestor of the present ruling imperial family. About AD 405, the Japanese court officially adopted the Chinese writing system. During the sixth century, Buddhism was introduced. These two events revolutionized Japanese culture and marked the beginning of a long period of Chinese cultural influence. From the establishment of the first fixed capital at Nara in 710 until 1867, the emperors of the Yamato dynasty were the nominal rulers, but actual power was usually held by powerful court nobles, regents, or "shoguns" (military governors).]]></dsc>
		<cities><![CDATA[<rows><row><cell>Tokyo</cell><cell>8483050</cell><cell>56</cell><cell>74</cell></row><row><cell>Yokohama</cell><cell>3643641</cell><cell>49</cell><cell>66</cell></row><row><cell>Sapporo</cell><cell>1896704</cell><cell>83</cell><cell>37</cell></row><row><cell>Kawasaki</cell><cell>1385003</cell><cell>47</cell><cell>53</cell></row><row><cell>Hiroshima</cell><cell>1164885</cell><cell>74</cell><cell>56</cell></row><row><cell>Chiba</cell><cell>943568</cell><cell>41</cell><cell>30</cell></row></rows>]]></cities>
		<chart><![CDATA[<data><item id="3"><year>2002</year><sales>3</sales></item><item id="4"><year>2003</year><sales>9</sales></item><item id="5"><year>2004</year><sales>4</sales></item><item id="6"><year>2005</year><sales>4</sales></item><item id="7"><year>2006</year><sales>7</sales></item><item id="8"><year>2007</year><sales>9</sales></item><item id="9"><year>2008</year><sales>6</sales></item><item id="10"><year>2009</year><sales>3</sales></item><item id="11"><year>2010</year><sales>5</sales></item><item id="12"><year>2011</year><sales>6</sales></item></data>]]></chart>
	</item>
	<item id="20">
		<img>norway.png</img>
		<name>Norway</name>
		<area>385,199 sq km</area>
		<capital>Oslo</capital>
		<language>Norwegian</language>
		<lat>61.965</lat>
		<lng>9.353</lng>
		<zoom>6</zoom>
		<dsc><![CDATA[The Viking period (9th to 11th centuries) was one of national unification and expansion. The Norwegian royal line died out in 1387, and the country entered a period of union with Denmark. By 1586, Norway had become part of the Danish Kingdom. In 1814, as a result of the Napoleonic wars, Norway was separated from Denmark and combined with Sweden. The union persisted until 1905, when Sweden recognized Norwegian independence.</p><p>The Norwegian Government offered the throne of Norway to Danish Prince Carl in 1905. After a plebiscite approving the establishment of a monarchy, the parliament unanimously elected him king. He took the name of Haakon VII, after the kings of independent Norway. Haakon died in 1957 and was succeeded by his son, Olav V, who died in January 1991. Upon Olav's death, his son Harald was crowned as King Harald V. Norway was a nonbelligerent during World War I, but as a result of the German invasion and occupation during World War II, Norwegians generally became skeptical of the concept of neutrality and turned instead to collective security. Norway was one of the signers of the North Atlantic Treaty in 1949 and was a founding member of the United Nations. The first UN General Secretary, Trygve Lie, was a Norwegian. Under the terms of the will of Alfred Nobel, the Storting (Parliament) elects the five members of the Norwegian Nobel Committee who award the Nobel Peace Prize to champions of peace. ]]></dsc>
		<cities><![CDATA[<rows><row><cell>Oslo</cell><cell>590041</cell><cell>76</cell><cell>91</cell></row><row><cell>Bergen</cell><cell>223593</cell><cell>57</cell><cell>60</cell></row><row><cell>Trondheim</cell><cell>156794</cell><cell>44</cell><cell>29</cell></row><row><cell>Stavanger</cell><cell>119276</cell><cell>71</cell><cell>43</cell></row><row><cell>Drammen</cell><cell>62815</cell><cell>57</cell><cell>38</cell></row><row><cell>Asker</cell><cell>54890</cell><cell>49</cell><cell>51</cell></row></rows>]]></cities>
		<chart><![CDATA[<data><item id="3"><year>2002</year><sales>6</sales></item><item id="4"><year>2003</year><sales>4</sales></item><item id="5"><year>2004</year><sales>7</sales></item><item id="6"><year>2005</year><sales>6</sales></item><item id="7"><year>2006</year><sales>2</sales></item><item id="8"><year>2007</year><sales>7</sales></item><item id="9"><year>2008</year><sales>10</sales></item><item id="10"><year>2009</year><sales>10</sales></item><item id="11"><year>2010</year><sales>9</sales></item><item id="12"><year>2011</year><sales>11</sales></item></data>]]></chart>
	</item>
</data>